- Don't
- What?
I can just feel you about to say it
just don't say it
I think we should bail
Benny, it's too late for that
- C'mon Claire, we.. we don't know what we're dealing here
-I do
- No, you don't!
- Yes, I do!
I really do okay, that thing fell out of the sky into our laps
i mean, to me that's a sign, okay?
What makes you so sure that the sign
is pointing in the right direction
You make me sure
Cause you got it to work
Always said that we deserve better, right?
So, i don't wanna wait for somebody to give us a chance
it's time that we took a chance for ourselves
I hope you're right
I am, i'm always right
I'm always right about you
- Okay
Okay
Sub by : maXeer
Movie Corner
ITEM 47
What you're looking at is Allentown, Pennsylvania
five days after the Battle of New York
This is a worst case scenario
Please tell me why is the one piece of Alien techie
failed to capture is now functioning
There are four confirmed reports of similar incidence
Richmond, Virginia
Seven days after the Battle of New York
Queensbury, North Carolina
Two days after that
Charleston, South Carolina
the following afternoon
Pasadena, Georgia
Yesterday morning
I had been there
it do a great pool park
right down the street
I don't think you're taking this
assignment very seriously
That's funny, i was just thinking
the same thing about you
While you've been in here gathering video clips
I've been out investigating
It turns out a used 28 foot Pearson
was taken off the marker in Key West
Spoke to the former owner,
a couple matching our description paid in cash
Boat gets out of Dry Dock in 24 hours
so, i'd like to get a move on
I understand, Agent Coulson
I'm sorry, force of habit
We all miss him
Your orders, Agent Sitwell
Retrieve the weapons tech
and neutralise ...the two outlaws
Thing's a killer on the wrist
feels i'm getting advanced carpal tunnel or something
What?
We did it
How much?
Enough
Enough enough?
Enough to do whatever we want
Now and forever
What the hell is that?
Oh, i like that song
Can you please...
Yup, okay.. okay, i'll say something
Just stay right there, don't move, i'll be right back
Hello?
Please stop squirming
Claire, it's the cops
Hit the deck, baby
Ay, my wrist...
- Benny, Benny are you okay?
- Claire
She go a lot cooler
Benny?
..do you even khow why we were in the room?
...yes, i do know what i was doing
We're gonna get arrested
Hi, hi.. i'm so sorry about before
i hope i didn't
hurt u..? 47 known alien objects hit the ground
after the portal closed above Manhattan
All dormant, all dead
execpt this one
This one works just fine
Any idea why that is?
Benny got it to work
What? you did
- Well i can show you how to do it
- show him, show him up
- He can show you really really
- Totally
- He would love to show you
- Just anything, but we can't.. we can't go to jail
- Look at him, he can't go to jail
- Who said anything about jail?
I was sent here to retrieve the weapon
and to neutralise you
Where the hell have you been?
Report was due 10 hours ago
42,000$ worth a damage at the motel, you know i've..
... gotten fury breathing down my neck..
Hi
Agent Blake, i'd like you to meet
Claire Wise and Benjamin Pollack
Benjamin here is the latest addition to the SHIELD R&D think tech
He's gonna help us reverse engineer some of the alien tech
- You ready to get that badge?
- Yess
Aaah, hold on a second Sitwell..
Oh, i forgot to mention
Claire is your new assistant
What
I mean, prodigy
Ya, that's ridiculous
Impart upon her all the knowledge and skills
that have made you the man you are today
Well, we don't even have another chair here
Now, that's ridiculous
- Sitwell, Sitwell...
Sitwell!
Hey..
Do you know how to make coffee?
No!
Sub by : maXeer
Movie Corner